<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Big Bang Evolution]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Big Bang Evolution]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/big-bang-evolution/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2016 19:23:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/big-bang-evolution/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Spirit and heredity]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Spirit and heredity</h1><p>Apart from hereditary gene structures and DNA spirals, the spirit, as a carrier of information, is a mechanism controlling organic life. Little by little DNA secrets and chromosome structures are unravelled and described. The creation of life through generic and sexless reproduction is a fascinating event. In a strictly ordered fashion the conjugation of tiny differentiated cells creates a beautiful, new and complete life. Each group of cells grows into a specialist cell structure of tissue or organs, according to a structured plan of development. In its first stages, the human embryo is very similar to other forms of animal life. Their mutual origins are clearly present. Cells differentiate and specialise rapidly. This process of biochemical interaction between hereditary material and cell division is controlled by a great cooperative complex. Commands are given and executed with a high degree of precision. This process can well be called a logistic miracle. A brilliant time schedule in addition to a high level of predictability of the end result. Memory plays a crucial part too. Chromosomes carry hereditary information. As the saying goes: history repeats itself. History is stored and passed on. It is hard to imagine that a few specific combinations of amino acids and bases can instigate and control such a complex history of reproduction. The elementary DNA material forms the biochemical key to the production of related proteins that react to become chains of amino acids and other organic matter. The dimensionless spirit wanders around this matter, governing the process of life with its imaginary sequence of numbers full of memory. Like an all-encompassing cocoon it communicates with matter. Processes of reproduction are not unique, they happen all the time in different places at different times as well as simultaneously. The uniformity of the process is biochemically controlled by genetic material and by number sequences that recorded the values of energies and reactions in memory keys. The memory key with number sequences acts like a catalyst for the development of the process. The correct value for the correct dosage prompt a reaction. These correct values are obtained through a continuous and intelligent learning process by the spirit. What is the most balanced step in the process that renders the best continuation? The selection and permanent adjustment of memory values ensure an organism can develop.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/big-bang-evolution/spirit-and-heredity/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">edb7e515-1d4b-4292-a7d5-989758e60bdd</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2016 19:22:51 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[About me]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>About me</h1><p>The world according to the Spirit.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/big-bang-evolution/1c39952c-72ad-4a69-afe1-e0ff7ffaa189/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">1c39952c-72ad-4a69-afe1-e0ff7ffaa189</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2016 19:17:57 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>The period before, during and after the Big Bang. There was evolution even before the Big Bang by the Spirit.The Spirit is a cocoon to organize matter versus anti-matter and the Big Bang. The Spirit is the leading motor for evolution of nature constants, values of nature laws plus evolution of matter, live and spiritual conscious. A total new concept for (meta) physics.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/big-bang-evolution/15351b53-af96-4855-b987-f2198c42434c/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">15351b53-af96-4855-b987-f2198c42434c</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2016 19:12:58 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>